{
    "id": "200827a5361247979dfc556fe2e13db8",
    "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Trees ………………… their leaves in autumn.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shed",
                "are shedding"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9a90a8473d624dd6bd17e6f5f672537d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………….. in her room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gets dressed",
                "is getting dressed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a98f1c10e5fb4fc2a1c18ec5e1ba829e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Water ………………. at 100 degree Celsius.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "boils",
                "is boiling"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b7db60e2fe25456cb299a02c6c9739d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The postman ………………… letters.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bring",
                "brings",
                "is bringing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06da9b94b5fe4795a8efe89277bf8a41"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Is dinner ready?’ ‘No I ………………….. it.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cook",
                "am cooking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ab115f70f774c58a8787b44d4c46055"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. a meeting this evening",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "address",
                "am addressing",
                "is addressing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e7ceeffa99d44bf6aa7057fc38a2bd38"
        },
        {
            "question": "The scriptures …………………. us that we must strive to conquer our ego.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tell",
                "tells",
                "is telling"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "36af367a0a174506bf49261ea5efc0e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… for the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "prepare",
                "am preparing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "47db131193404b15be5bfbc2ea1c9737"
        },
        {
            "question": "The students …………………. on the project.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "are working"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8053f43e3b404e36b04fd562a4b2505d"
        },
        {
            "question": "My brother ………………….. his examination on Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "write",
                "writes",
                "is writing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6f46f92112f24a408fa817216584dd9b"
        }
    ]
}